VINOD VAMAN BHAT

vinodvamanbhat@gmail.com | +91 8806048503

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/vinod-bhat-5267641b5/

Personal Website - https://snazzy-tartufo-6f8f42.netlify.app/

GitHub - https://github.com/VVB2

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

PROFILE

3 years of experience as Full Stack Web Developer and 2 years of experience as DevOps Engineer. Experience in designing, developing & troubleshooting software code using ReactJS for software components of web applications. Hands-on Experience in NoSQL Database -MongoDB also in Docker and AWS. Gained Practical Knowledge of Linux Commands and implemented a production NodeJS environment on a fresh server.

EXPERIENCE

ZEEVE

Intern, Mumbai, India

Jan 2022 - April 2022

- I created a DevOps pipeline from scratch.
- I helped create a GitLab runner that automates the deployment of Docker images with a simple command.
- Helped the team to design the pipeline in question.
- Kubernetes, Docker, GitLab.

CMP INFOTECH Intern, Mumbai, India

April 2021 -May 2021

- User Details Registration using JAVA
- JavaFx
- Gluon Scene builder

PROJECTS

MOCK TEST WEBSITE

Personal Project

Website to test your programming knowledge by giving mock MCQ tests build using Flask, MySql, and ChartJS.

Feb 2021 -May 2021

E-COMMERCE **WEBSITE**

Personal Project

July 2021 -Sep 2021

Created an E-Commerce website to buy artifacts using React, Material-UI, React-Stripe as frontend and Express as backend and MongoDB as database, StripeJS for payment gateway.

PRODUCTION WEB Leisure and Cultural Services Department

PAGE

Sep 2022 -

Sep 2022

Created a production-ready web page for the Leisure and Cultural Services Department (Government of Hong Kong) to track the number of visitors coming to the venue using React, Ant design as frontend, and Express as backend, and Nginx as the webserver.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages Python, Shell, JavaScript, SQL, HTML5, PHP, CSS.

Frameworks React, Flask, Jinja2, Next.

Storage MySQL, MongoDB.

Version Control Git, GITLAB.

DevOps Docker, Kubernetes, Helm.

Platforms Linux, GCP, Heroku, Windows, AWS.

EDUCATION

BE (Information Technology Engineering)	Xavier Institute of Engineering Mumbai, Maharashtra	06/2023
HSC	VIVA College Mumbai, Maharashtra	06/2019
SSC	ST John XXIII High School Mumbai, Maharashtra	06/2017

CERTIFICATIONS AND PUBLICATIONS

DevOps	 Good understanding of CI/CD workflows which is the main concern of any production deployment. Got a hands-on experience with Docker, Kubernetes. Understood the concepts of Containerization, Images, Clusters as well as Load Balancing.
Workshop	 Understood the core concepts of JAVA programming language. Got an idea of all the fields and places where JAVA can be a better fit compared to other programming languages.